Piyush Shrivastava

Full Stack Developer



□ piyushshri924@gmail.com

\(09806309139

• H. N. 223 A Gopal Nagar Bhopal (M. P.)

1 09/09/1990

https:/github.com/PiyushShri9990

■ INDIA

Profile

Passionate and experienced Event Planner bringing forth several years of experience planning, coordinating, and overseeing various sorts of events. To work in a competent environment that would enable to cope with the emerging business trends and technologies and widen the spectrum of my knowledge to add value to the individual growth.

Education

BCA, *Rajeev Gandhi College Raisen(M.P.)* 06/2011 – 04/2016 | Raisen, India

Higher Secondary,

Shining Public School Raisen 07/2010 – 03/2011 | Raisen, India

Projects

Spotify 2

PDFMergerApp ☑

KonTestApp ☑

Professional Experience

Trainer, *Jetking* 10/2021 – 06/2022 | Bhopal, India

Development, *Suntec* 12/2018 – 02/2020 | Noida, India

Technical Support, *Airtel* 05/2015 – 11/2018 | Delhi, India

Customer Service Associate, First Source LTD Bhopal 10/2014 – 04/2015 | Bhopal, India

Skills

JavaScript, HTML & CSS, ReactJs, NodeJs (MERN), Angular (MEAN), Java, Java(j2se), MySQL, MongoDB, .Net Frame Work

Courses

Java (J2se), JavaScript, *Ezeon Tech* Bhopal, India

DBMS Packages : MySql, MongoDB., *Ezeon Tech*Bhopal, India

Web Designing: HTML, CSS, *Ezeon Tech* Bhopal, India

.Net, Ace Software Development PVT. LTD Bhopal, India

Cyber Security (Ethical Hacking)., *Jetking* Bhopal, India

Hardware And Networking, CCNA, *Jetking* Bhopal, India

Declaration

I hereby declare that above-mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above mentioned particulars.

Piyush ShrivastavaBhopal